A Guide to the Black Organizations Council Records, 1982-2017
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
Black Organizations Council Records, 1982-2017
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech, Blacksburg, Va.
RG 8/2/6e
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
The collection is open for research. Access to unredacted BOC and BGSO administrative records is restricted. Contact Special Collections and University Archives for more information.
Acquisition Information
The Black Organizations Council Records were transferred to Special Collections and University Archives in 2017.
Biographical Note/Administrative History
Founded on the Virginia Tech campus in 1985, the Black Organizations Council (BOC) is the umbrella and resource body for the Black student organizations. BOC serves to ensure the betterment of the Black community through providing a unified voice for the Black community in a university population where the Black community lacks adequate representation. BOC also serves as a liaison between the administration, university organizations, and the Black community, provides a forum for the exchange of ideas and dissemination of information, promotes the Black organizations individually and collectively, coordinates events which require the participation of all entities of the Black community and supports the development of campus camaraderie within the university community. BOC has a mission of being the governing, representing, and coordinating body for the primarily African American student organizations. We will also provide activism and advocacy, while meeting the challenge of the social and political forces affecting the Black community. We encourage each representative organization to empower themselves to create a paradigm in the area of leadership and service in the community.
Source: BOC GobblerConnect page, https://gobblerconnect.vt.edu/organization/BOC.
Content Description
This collection contains video cassette tapes of events and programs relating to the Black community at Virginia Tech and programs of other minority groups. It also contains 3 boxes of pictures of events and programs relating to minority groups at Virginia Tech. The events documented include Black History Month programs, the Donning of the Kente ceremony, Multicultural Center events, Hispanic Heritage Month, Asian American Student Union cultural heritage programs, book signings, and guest speakers. There are also pictures of various faculty, staff, and students. Additionally, the collection contains flyers and calendars from the Black Organizations Council and related organizations, a binder of slides of paintings, drawings, and portraits, accounting documents, a history of events booklet, and folders of records, minutes, and other documents.
Arrangement
The collections has been divided into six series.
Series 1: Black Organizations Council Operations includes documents related to the running of the Black Organizations Council. This series is divided into four subseries: administrative files, meeting agendas and minutes, photographs, and financial records.
Subseries 1: Administrative Files includes the organiation's constitution, information about its constitutent member organizations, policies and guidelines, officer elections paperwork, meeting sign-in sheets, and other administrative information.
Subseries 2: Meeting Agendas and Minutes includes the minutes of general body and executive board meetings, the campus programming committee, and meetings with president Steger.
Subseries 3: Photographs includes an organizational scrapbook and a digital record of photographs of organization members and events.
Subseries 4: Financial Records includes budget requests and other financial records.
Series 2: Member Organizations includes photographs and other records related to student organizations that were members of the Black Organizations Council. This series has one subseries: Black Graduate Student Organization.
Subseries 1: Black Graduate Student Organization includes photographs, administrative papers, event flyers, and other materials about the Black Graduate Student Organization.
Series 3: Other Campus Organizations includes constitutions from the Jewish Student Union, University Council, and Student Budget Board as well as materials about the Interfraternity Council, the Asian American Student Union, and the Cultural Centers Advisory Committee.
Series 4: Events includes information about event planning by the Black Organizations Council, videos and photographs of events hosted in whole or in part by the Black Organizations Council, and videos and photographs of events hosted by other campus organizations. This series has nine subseries: Afrikan Awareness Weekend, Asian American Student Union, Black History Month, Black Student Leadership, Celebration of Diversity, Donning of the Kente, Filipino-American Student Association Culture Night, State of the Black Union, and Other Events.
Subseries 1: Afrikan Awareness Weekend includes videos of the 1990 and 1991 Afrikan Awareness Weekend events.
Subseries 2: Asian American Student Union includes videos and photographs of events hosted by the Asian American Student Union.
Subseries 3: Black History Month includes videos and photographs of Black History Month events.
Subseries 4: Black Student Leadership includes photographs of the 1999 Student Leadership Institute and the 2002 Carroll F. S. Hardy National Black Student Leadership Development Conference.
Subseries 5: Celebration of Diversity includes videos and photographs of the Celebration of Diversity event, primarily those held on September 12, 2001 and September 11, 2002.
Subseries 6: Donning of the Kente includes a video, photographs, programs, registrations forms, and other planning records related to the Donning of the Kente graduation event.
Subseries 7: Filipino-American Student Association Culture Night includes videos of the Filipino-American Student Association's Culture Nights from 1997 and 1998.
Subseries 8: State of the Black Union includes documentation and student feedback posters related to the State of the Black Union event.
Subseries 9: Other Events includes videos, photographs, and documents related to other events including An African American Food Taste, Black Organizations Showcase, Black Student Preview, Ebony Affair, Hispanic Heritage Month, Kwanzaa, Million Man March, Relay for Life, Safe Zone Reception, Virginia Nations Pow Wow, White Ribbon Campaign, and others.
Series 5: Presentations and Resources includes research from presentations given by members of the Black Organizations Council and materials maintained by the Black Organizations Council as resources for its membership.
Series 6: Black Cultural Center and Multicultural Center includes photographs of these two centers. This series has three subseries: Displays, Internal and External Views, and Faculty, Staff, and Students.
Subseries 1: Displays includes mounted photographs from center displays and photographs of displays set up by the centers.
Subseries 2: Internal and External Views includes internal and external photographs of the two centers.
Subseries 3: Faculty, Staff, and Students includes photographs of people who are associated with the centers.
Separated Materials
2006 Future campus master plan map
Gender.org Gender Variance primer
Virginia Tech Governance Structure diagram
Commission on Student Affairs meeting agenda
Commission on Student Affairs member list
CEOD Resolution 2009-10 A Revision to Policy 1025
Campus Climate questionnaire
HTM 3044: Private Club Management Syllabus
Dept. of Communications Cognate Approval form
CLAHS B.S. in Human Development course requirements for graduating in 2016
Index Terms
Subjects:
University Archives; African American history; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University; Johnson, Nicole
- Operational Records, 1984-2016
  - Administrative Files, 1984-2013
    - Constitution, 1984-2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Member Organizations Information (Redacted), n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Member Organizations Information (Unredacted), n.d. (Folder 4)
    - Pamphlets, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Information, 1989-2009 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Administrative Binder, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Policies and Guidelines, 2002-2012 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Calendars and Schedules, 1989-2013 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Elections Paperwork (Redacted), 2000-2010 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Elections Paperwork (Unredacted), 2000-2010 (Folder 4)
    - Sign-in Sheets (Redacted), n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Sign-in Sheets (Unredacted), n.d. (Folder 4)
  - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1988-2010
    - General Body Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 2005-09-21-2009-11-19 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Executive Board Agendas and Minutes, 1988-2009 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Campus Programming Committee Minutes, 2010-10-21 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Meetings with President Steger, 2006, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, 2008
    - Black Organizations Council Pictures CD-ROM, 2008-09-29; 342.8 Megabytes One CD-ROM (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook: Fall/Spring 2008 (Box 10)
  - Financial Records, 1995-2016
    - University Chartered Student Organization (UCSO) Budget Manager Workshop, Funds Handling Policy, 2010-2016 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Black Organizations Council Budget Managers Workshop, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Accounting Records, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Accounting Records, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Accounting Records, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Accounting Records, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Accounting Records, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Accounting Records, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Accounting Records, 2009-2011 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Accounting Records, 1998-2016 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Member Organizations, 1995-2014
    - African Student Association (ASA) Photographs, 2001-10-31 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha (ΑΦΑ) Photographs, 2001-10-03 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Black Graduate Student Organization (BGSO), 1995-2014
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Administrative Papers (Redacted), 1998-09-2014 (Box 1, Folder 24)
      - Administrative Papers (Unredacted), 1998-09-2014 (Folder 4)
      - Pamphlets, 2002-2006 (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Event Flyers and Programs, 2012-2014 (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - Proclamation Plaque, 1995-1996 (Box 11)
    - Delta Sigma Theta (ΔΣΘ) Photographs, 2001-10-31 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Minorities in Agriculture, Natural Resources, and Related Sciences (MANRRS) Pictures for Black Student Orientation powerpoint (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Phi Beta Sigma (ΦΒΣ) Photographs, 2001-09-17 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Sigma Gamma Rho (ΣΓΡ) Photographs, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Zeta Phi Beta (ΖΦΒ) Photographs, 2001-10-31, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Other Campus Organizations, 1988-2007
    - Constitutions from Other Campus Organizations, 2007-01-12, 2007-10-01, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 27)
      Scope and Contents
      Includes constitutions from the Jewish Student Union (JSU), University Council, and Student Budget Board.
    - Interfraternity Council (IFC), 1988, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Asian American Student Union (AASU), 2000 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Cultural Centers Advisory Committee (CCAC) Photographs, Fall 2001 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Events, 1990-2015; 1995-2002
    - Event Planning, 1998-2016 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Black Organizations Council History of Events Booklet, 1990-2000 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Afrikan Awareness Weekend, 1990-1991
      - 1. Afrikan Awareness Weekend, "The Role of Black Students in Building Black Businesses", Dr. E. Curtis Alexander & Dr. LaFrancis Rodgers-Rose, 1990-02-03; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 2. 1st Afrikan Awareness Weekend, "Racism, White Supremacy vs. Black Liberation", Dr. Frances Cress Wesling, M.D.", 1990-02-03; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 3. Afrikan Awareness Weekend, "Self-Discovery 101: You Gotta Havit", Umoja Na Kazi Theatre Company, 1990-02-03; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 6. Afrikan Awareness Weekend, "Self-Discovery 101: You Gotta Havit", Umoja Na Kazi Theatre Company - Camera II, 1990-02-02; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 8. Afrikan Awareness Weekend, "Strategies for Resolving Conflicts in Male Female Relationships", Dr. LaFrancis Rose, 1990-02-02; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 9. 2nd Afrikan Awareness Weekend at Va Tech, Gordon + Bolling, 1990-02-02; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 11. Afrikan Awareness Weekend, "Self-Discovery 101: You Gotta Havit", Imoja Na Kazi Theatre Company, 1990-02-04; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 13. Afrikan Awareness Weekend, "Black Student Guide to Positive Education", Dr. Zak Kondo, 1990-02-03; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 15. 1st Afrikan Awareness Weekend, "Creative Writing as a Tool for Liberation". Dr. Opal Moore, 1990-02-03; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 16. Afrikan Awareness Weekend, "Black Student Guide to Positive Education", Dr. Zak Kondo, 1990-02-03; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 18. Afrikan Awareness Weekend, "The Endangered Black Male / The Bald Eagle", Dr. Jeffrey Jonnson, 1990-02-03; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 19. Afrikan Awareness Weekend, "Role of Religion in the Liberation of Black People", Closing Remarks, Dr. E. Curtis Alexander & Kwame Alexander, 1990-02-04; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 20. 2nd Afrikan Awareness Weekend at Va Tech, Keynote Address: Sonia Sanchez, 1991-02-01; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 22. 2nd Afrikan Awareness Weekend at Va Tech, Cox, Gay, and Fulani, 1991-02-02; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 23. 2nd Afrikan Awareness Weekend at Va Tech, Moore, Alexander, and Afetse, 1991-02-02; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 24. 2nd Afrikan Awareness Weekend at Va Tech, Plunky and Woody King, 1991-02-02; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 26. 2nd Afrikan Awareness Weekend at Va Tech, Sonya Sanchez, 1991-02-01; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 27. Dr. E. C. Alexander & Dr. LaFrancis Rodgers-Rose, "The Role of Black Students in Building Black Businesses", c.1991; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - 30. 2nd Afrikan Awareness Weekend at Va Tech, Bell, Subira, McKeever, 1991-02-02; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - Afrikan Awareness Weekend, 1991-02-04, "Role of Religion in the Liberation of Black People", Dr. E. Curtis Alexander, 1 VHS (Box 3)
    - Asian American Student Union, 1997-2001
      - Culture Night "Our Rising Tradition" Photographs, 1997-11-01 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - Cultural Exhibition Photographs, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - Culture Show Photographs, 2000-11-04 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - Culture Night Photographs, 2001-10-27 (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - 10th Annual Cultural Exhibition, 2001-10-27; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - RICE Concert Photographs, 2000-12-02-2000-12-03 (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Panel Photographs, 2001-04-30 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Black History Month, 1990-2002
      - First Black History Month Parade, "Keeping the Dream Alive", Community Awareness Council of Salem, VA, Produced by the staff of VTTV Channel 33, Blacksburg, VA, 1990-02-03; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - Planning Documents and Flyers, 1991, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - 7. Pearl Cleage, Black History Month, 1991-02-24; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - Photographs, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - Photographs, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - Program Photographs, 2000-01-27 (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - Lucinda Roy Book Signing Photographs, 2000-02-01 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - Costume Ball Photographs, 2000-02-01 (Box 6, Folder 21)
      - United States Representative Maxine Waters Photographs, 2000-02-03 (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Kip Fulbeck Photographs, 2000-02-23 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Finale Photographs, 2000-02-29 (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Judge Joe Brown Photographs, 2001-02-08 (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Black History Month Photographs, 2002-01-30-2002-02-11 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Black Student Leadership, 1999-2002
      - Student Leadership Institute Photographs, Fall 1999 (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Carroll F. S. Hardy National Black Student Leadership Development Conference Photographs, 2002-01-05 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Celebration of Diversity, 2000-2002, n.d.
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Video, 2000-08-30; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - Photographs, 2001-09-12 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Photographs, 2002-09-11 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Video, 2002-09-11; 1 VHS (Box 3)
    - Donning of the Kente, 1995-2002
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Photographs, Spring 1995 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Scrapbook: Donning of the Kente & Million Man March, 1995-1996, 2000 (Box 10)
      - Photographs, Spring 1997? (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - Programs and Planning Records, 1997-2011; 0.1 Cubic Feet 1 DVD, Papers (Box 1, Folder 33, Folder 34)
      - Photographs, 2000-05-12 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Photographs, 2000-12-15 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Photographs, 2001-05-11 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Photographs, 2001-12-21 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - Photographs, 2002-05-10 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Filipino-American Student Association Culture Night, 1997-1998
      - 9th Annual Cultural Night, Iba't-Ibang Kultura, Isang Identidad "Many Cultures, One Identity", 1997-04-05; 1 VHS (Box 5)
      - Tenth Annual Cultural Night, "A Decade of Making A Difference" 1988-1998, 1998-04-04; 1 VHS (Box 5)
    - State of the Black Union, 2011, 2015, n.d.
      - Programs and Flyers, 2011, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 35)
      - Response Posters, November 2015 (Folder 3)
        In fall of 2015, the Black Organizations Council held an event titled State of the Black Union: Do Black Lives Matter at Virginia Tech?. These posters were part of an associated community feedback event where students were asked to write their responses to the prompt "Why do Black Lives Matter at Virginia Tech?" The event took place a few months after racially charged protests at the University of Missouri and students here at Virginia Tech were eager to have their voices heard.
    - Other Events, 1995-2016
      - An African American Food Taste Photographs, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Biz Markie Featuring Run DMC, 1997-11-07; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - Black Cultural Center Quarter Drive Photographs, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Black Greek Speaker, Step Show, n.d.; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - Black Organizations Showcase Photographs, 1997-02 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Black Student Showcase, 1995-2015 (Box 1, Folder 36)
      - Black Student Preview, 2009, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 37)
      - Brian Collier Presentation Photographs, 2000-11-01 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Candlelight Vigil, 1997; 1 VHS (Box 3)
      - Celebrations Around the World Photographs, 2000-11-13 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - De LaVega Presentation Photographs, 2000-03-24 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Black Graduate Student Organization (BGSO) Ebony Affair, 1999-2015 (Box 1, Folder 38)
      - Hispanic Heritage Month: Solazo Photographs, 2001-09-14-2001-10-12 (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Kwanzaa Photographs, 2001-11-28 (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - March of the Living, n.d.; 1 VHS (Box 5)
      - Million Man March Photographs, 1995-10-16 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - The Music of Charles Mingus Event Poster, 2014-02-28 (Box 11)
        A concert poster signed by Charles Mingus and John D'earth. The event description from Facebook read: "Join the Virginia Tech Jazz Ensemble and special guest John D'earth in celebrating the music of Charles Mingus. This concert is presented in conjunction with the Office of Multicultural Programs' celebration of Black History Month. This performance will also feature the award winning jazz ensemble from Albemarle HS $5 Students/$8 Adults"
      - Project S.A.F.E. (Sexual Assault Facts & Education) Photographs, 2000-02-28 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Relay for Life, 2011 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Safe Zone Reception Photographs, 2000-02-04 (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Safe Zone Reception Photographs, Spring 2002 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Student Preview Photographs, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Theatrical Publicity Photographs for Mad at Miles, c.1990s (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Virginia Nations Pow Wow Photographs, 2002-02-23-2002-02-24 (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - White Ribbon Campaign Photographs, 2002-10-08 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Unidentified Event Photographs, 1998-1999 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Unidentified Event Photographs, 2000-05-04 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Unidentified Event Photographs, 2000-05-19 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Unidentified Event Photographs, 2000-08-30 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Unidentified Event Photographs, 2000-09-23 (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Unidentified Event Photographs, 2002-01-05 (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Miscellaneous Event Photographs, c.1999-c.2001 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Events Photographs Album, 1997-1998 (Box 9)
      - Event Signs and Posters, 2016, n.d. (Folder 1)
      - Event Trifold Poster Displays, n.d. (Folder 2)
  - Presentations and Resources, 1982-2008
    - Minority Newsletter, 1982-1983, Spring 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Diverse Issues in Higher Education Magazine, 2005-08-25 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Predominantly Black Churches List, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Admissions Applications and Degrees Awarded by Ethnicity, 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Jermaine Floyd "Appreciated Responses to Paper on Martin Luther King, Jr.", 2008-02-08 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Keeping Cultural Centers Relevant: One University's Approach, 2002-01-02; 0.255 Megabytes 1 3.5" Floppy (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Mixtapes, c.2005, 2008; 0.1 Cubic Feet 2 CDs (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - 4. Portrait of A Carribean Artist: Wilcox Morris, 1991-01; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - 5. Hampton University's "Don't Grieve After Me", n.d.; 1 VHS (Box 5)
    - 21. Alex Bostic Paintings, n.d.; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - 28. Dr. Molefi Kete Asante, n.d.; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - 29. The Consortium of Musicians Presents Spirituals of the Invisible Church, Dr. Jester Hairston, Directing, Consortium of Musicians, 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - Kindred Spirits: Contemporary African-American Artists, Presented By Phillip Morris Companies, Inc., 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - Artwork slides, 1989-1993 (Box 9)
    - Legacies of Resistance and Survival: The First Black Women Students at Virginia Tech, 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - Legacies of Resistance and Survival, Workprint, 2000-05-01; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - How Can We Help Each Other?, n.d.; 2 Cassettes 2 VHS (Box 4)
    - How Can We Help Each Other? Part I, 1994-04-21; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - Virginia Tech: A Community of Conscience, 1997 Update, 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - VT Video, Summer Orientation '98, 1998; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - VT Video, 2004; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - Beyond the Dream, 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - BSA Film's Com., Rod Roger's Dance Troop / Ain't I a Woman, Ezibu Muntu, n.d.; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - Condoms & Common Sense, Modern Education Services, Inc., Sponsored by: Carter-Wallace, Inc., 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - Creative Dating Workshop, Coleman Productions, n.d.; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - KRS-One Footage / Off Tha Hook Footage, KRS-One Lecture - Back off room (No Volume), n.d.; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - Michael Dyson vs. Dinesh D'Souza, International Lecture Management, n.d.; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - The People's Court, Judge Marilyn Milian Introduction, n.d.; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - Saint Johns University, Experience College, RT: 15:00, n.d.; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - Saturday Night Live: Michael Jordan & Public Enemy, Fall 1991; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - VISION 2000, Russell-McCloud & Associates, 1994-04-13; 1 VHS (Box 4)
    - Your Voice Television Talk Show, Highlights of the 1st Season, Florida State University College of Education, n.d.; 1 VHS (Box 4)
  - Black Cultural Center and Multicultural Center, 1999-2001
    - Mounted photographs from Multicultural Center Reunion, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Hall Display Case Photographs, Fall 1999 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Black Cultural Center Display Photographs, Spring 1999-Fall 1999 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Multicultural Center Display Photographs, Fall 1999 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Photographs, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 6)